我正在把微流控通道里的电渗流流速
Okay, I'm zeroing out the electro-osmotic flow rate
给归零了
in the micro-fluidic channel.
干得漂亮  霍华德
Nicely done, Howard.
我老婆身高147公分  性生活和谐
Well, my wife is four-foot-ten and sexually satisfied,
很明显能看出我对于小东西很有一套
so clearly I know my way around tiny things.
给你点赞  在尖端新科技之前
Good for you, on the cutting edge of new technology
还能继续开这种
and still making inappropriate comments
不尊重你孩子母亲的玩笑
about the mother of your child.
你听到的  还只是我说出口的"干净版"呢
Those are just the things I say out loud.
先生们  我们得立即停工
Gentlemen, we need to stop immediately.
出什么事了
What's wrong?
我看着这算式
I'm looking at the math,
我觉得我们能够做出
and I think we can make the device
比现有版本小8到10%的仪器
between eight and ten percent smaller.
很好啊  可是空军已经同意之前的规格了
That's great, but the Air Force approved the specs.
我们可以继续做下去了
We're good to go.
对啊  没必要把它再做更小
Yeah. It doesn't need to be smaller.
你们要不要脸了
Shame on you.
要是贵宾犬繁殖者都是你们这态度会怎么样
Where would we be if poodle breeders had that attitude?
我来告诉你们
I'll tell you.
我们现在只会有标准型跟迷你型贵宾犬
We would have the standard and the miniature poodle,
不会有玩具型跟茶杯型
but no toy or teacup.
顺带一说
Which by the way,
茶杯型并不是官方承认的品种
is not an officially recognized breed,
不过这都是贵宾犬界的事了
but that's just poodle politics.
我们能不能不聊贵宾犬了
Can we please stop talking about poodles?
行啊  巧克力棒
Fine. Candy bars.
你喜欢迷你版的吗  我知道你喜欢
Now, do you enjoy a fun size? I know you do.
谢尔顿  我们不需要把它做得更小了
Sheldon, we don't need to make this smaller.
你的职责已经完成了  回家吧
Your work is done. Go home.
我不想回家
I don't want to go home.
行  那你去散个步吧
Fine, go for a little walk.
然后呢
Then what?
你就一直走别停就对了
Just keep walking.
至少他去洗手间时这里很清静
At least it's quiet when he takes bathroom breaks.
我知道啊
I know.
所以我才总在他不注意时  往他水杯里添水
That's why I keep refilling his water when he's not looking.
你是在开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
就算加水加到干旱  也是值得的
I don't care if we're in a drought, it's worth it.
其实我还真有个方法可以摆脱他
You know, I-I do have a way to get him out of our hair.
我已经把这招留着几年了
I've been holding onto this for a few years,
或许现在是时候了
but maybe now's the time.
我们锁上门也行啊  不用为此宰了他吧
W-We can just lock the door; you don't have to kill him.
我们才杀不了他
You can't kill him;
他会在最后一次存档的点重生
he'll just respawn at the last save point.
这是我第六次去上厕所了
Oh, that was my sixth trip to the bathroom.
反正不是因为尿路感染就好
As long as that's not a urinary tract infection,
这可是我个人新纪录呢
that's a personal best.
兄弟  我有个礼物给你
Hey, uh, buddy, I got you a little present.
-是吗  -对啊
- Really? - Yeah.
来吧  打开它
Go ahead, open it.
"恭喜您
"Congratulations.
这张证书的持有者将有机会
The bearer of this certificate is entitled
享受终极火车体验
to the ultimate train experience
地点在内华达北部铁路
at The Nevada Northern Railway.
您将能进驾驶舱
You are at the throttle.
您将会是驾驶员
You are the engineer.
由您来驾驶火车头"
You are running the locomotive."
这事很少发生
This doesn't happen very often,
但大抱抱要来啦
but here comes a hug.
妈呀  我又得去尿了
Oh, dear! I have to tinkle again!
好啦  我们刚才进行到哪了
Okay. Where were we?
填华仔的职业时
For Howie's occupation,
我该把宇航员也写进去吗
should I include that he was an astronaut?
他甚至在他妈的悼词里都提了  就写吧
Well, he mentioned it in his mother's eulogy, so why not?
我真不敢相信你得为一个婴儿
I can't believe you have to fill out
开始填幼儿园的申请表
a preschool application for an infant.
加州理工那间候补名单超级长
Uh, the one at Caltech has a crazy wait list.
我提醒过你  很多人怀孕时就开始申请了
I warned you, a lot of people apply when they're still pregnant.
是是是  我没申请
Well, I didn't.
我还逃了分娩课去看《疯狂动物城》  所以闭嘴吧
I also skipped a birthing class to see Zootopia, so back off.
我只是想帮忙而已
Whoa. Just trying to help.
对不起啦  华仔回去工作了
Sorry. Howie's back at work
而手边的事情又太多了
and there's just so much going on.
有什么事我们能帮你的吗
Is there anything we can do?
有啊  开个大学学费账户
Sure. Open up a college fund,
去挑人寿保险  然后洗衣房里
shop for life insurance, and in the laundry room,
还有堆积如山的脏衣服
there's a mountain of dirty laundry.
洗了还是烧了  随你选
Wash it or burn in, your choice.
马上回来
Ugh, be right back.
不用不用  我来处理
No, no. I will take care of it.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
我不在的时候  你刚好有时间反省一下
While I'm gone, you can think about
你对我的态度有多恶劣
how mean you were to me.
好啦  你知道你需要什么吗
All right, you know what you need?
一个抛开这一切的夜晚
A night away from all of this.
你可以放松心情
You know, where you can just kind of relax and...
我就先...  把这个关掉了
I'm just gonna... turn this off.
好多了
Much better.
说认真的  来安排一个晚上
Seriously, let's plan a night,
给自己放个假
you know, give you a break.
我们可以一起去蹦迪啊
We could go dancing.
听起来很有意思
That sounds really nice.
这个礼拜帕萨迪纳市中世纪音乐社团要跟
All this week, the Early Music Society of Pasadena
圣盖博市文艺复兴合唱团联合举办音乐会
is doing a joint concert with the San Gabriel Renaissance Choir.
行  没更好的就这个了
Okay, that's the one to beat.
找到更好的谈何容易
Good luck.
世人们想超越他们都试了足足六百年了
People have been saying that for 600 years.
你今天回家好早
Hey, you're home early.
说出来你绝对不信
You'll never believe it.
莱纳德给了我一份超棒的礼物
Leonard gave me the most incredible gift,
历史古迹铁路游
a trip to a historic railway,
而且我还能亲自驾驶火车头
and I get to operate an actual locomotive.
他终于使出压箱底的招了
Wow. He finally used it.
你做啥了
What'd you do?
我也不知道
No idea.
我只知道我马上要在铁路工作
All I know is I'm gonna be working on the railroad
整天整日哟
all the livelong day.
我真的很为你高兴
Well, I'm really happy for you.
别  别光为我高兴呀
Oh, no. It's not just me. No.
铁路离最近的机场有四小时的车程呢
The railway is four hours from the nearest airport,
猜猜谁有这荣幸载我去
and guess who gets to drive me.
我弃权
I give up.
你啊
You!
不  我真的弃权
No. I really give up.
对了  猜猜我们可以住哪里
Oh, oh. And guess where we get to sleep?
我们的选择有  19世纪末20世纪初建的铁路宿舍
Our choice of a turn-of-the-century railway bunkhouse
或载货火车的工作守车
or a working caboose.
守车的问题是  里面没有洗手间
Now, the problem with a caboose is there's no bathroom,
简易宿舍的问题是  它不是守车
but the problem with the bunkhouse is it's not a caboose.
第一天
On the first day,
我可以开蒸汽机火车
I get to drive a steam engine.
第二天是柴油机火车
Oh, and the second day, a diesel engine.
还有还有
Oh, and
如果我自愿做轨道养护和文书工作
if I volunteer to do track maintenance and paperwork,
那我想在那待多久都行
they'll let me stay as long as I want.
所以你最好带的衣服够我们余生穿
So you might want to pack enough clothes for the rest of our lives.
我现在可以尿尿了吗
Can I pee now?
听这个
Oh, get this!
我还能参加考试  试题出自一本125页的手册
I get to take a test based on a 125-page manual.
我可以学很多东西  比如手势信号
I get to learn things like hand signals.
前进  倒车
There's forward, uh, reverse,
刹车
set the brakes.
你完事了没
Are you done yet?
你错过了一些很赞的东西
You're missing some great stuff out here.
这个太赞了
Oh, this is good.
那里有许多铁路公路交叉口
There are dozens of railroad crossings
你必须得吹哨子指挥
you have to blow the whistle for.
我说的"你"是泛指  不是真的指你本人
But that is the figurative you, not the literal you.
我才是吹哨子那个
I'll be blowing the whistle.
艾米  起床  该上班了
Amy, get up. It's time to go to work.
火车的吸引力比我想象中还要大
This train thing worked out better than I thought.
他现在在家学习火车驾驶员手册呢
He's home studying the engineer's manual.
他不在  真的好安静啊
It's so peaceful without him here.
我能问问花了你多少钱吗
Can I ask you how much that cost?
四千大洋  每一分都花得值
$4,000-- worth every penny.
先生们
Gentlemen.
-威廉姆斯上校  -先生
- Colonel Williams. - Sir.
过来看看导向系统进展如何
Just wanted to see how the guidance system's coming along.
很好  我们研究出一个冷却方案
Great. We found a cooling solution
可以让原型机的大小
that allowed us to get the size of the prototype
缩小至目标规格
down to the target specs.
这个冷却方案  是不是很酷[冷]呢
As a cooling solution, it's pretty cool.
别开冷笑话
Don't do that.
这是什么
What's this?
没什么  一些我们用不着的数学
Oh, nothing. Just some math we don't need.
这是另一种方案
This is a different approach.
你们是想把这个导向系统做得更小吗
Are you trying to get the guidance system even smaller?
这只是纸上谈兵
It's just a theory.
还没有实践成功呢
Uh, it's not even worked out.
我要这个方案
I want this.
但我们已经做到之前约定的规格了
But we've already met the agreed upon specs.
将规格变小需要花好几周重新计算
Going smaller would require weeks' worth of new computations.
那就让那个长袖套短袖的小孩做啊
So get the kid with the two shirts to do it.
现在  请容许我说一句  我们已经花费
Sir, uh, I-if I may, uh, we've put a lot
大量的心思和功夫在现在这台原型机上
of thought and effort into this current prototype.
这真的是一个完美的方案了
It's a really elegant solution,
最重要的是  它可以实现
and most importantly, it works.
我知道  我就要这个方案
Yeah, I want this.
但那个方案只是纸上谈兵
But that's just a theory.
甚至称不上是一个完整的构思
It's not even a complete thought.
你们俩说得都非常有道理
You both make excellent points.
感谢你们如此清晰地表达出来
And thank you for presenting it so articulately.
把这个方案做出来
Make this.
那个长袖套短袖的小屁孩再一次祸害了我们
The kid with the two shirts screwed us again.
好了  你们俩准备好疯狂玩乐了吗
All right. You guys ready to get crazy?
今天穿的可不是肉色内衣哦
Well, the bra under here ain't beige.
好了
Okay.
你们女士今晚好好玩
You ladies have fun tonight.
别担心哈雷  有斯尔图特叔叔呢
Don't worry about Halley. Uncle Stuart's on the job.
她的教父会密切监控他的工作
Under the careful supervision of her godfather.
抱歉  我无意冒犯你  唐·柯里昂
My apologies. I didn't mean to offend you, Don Corleone.
我都说啦  你们好好玩
Like I said, you ladies have fun.
会的  舞鞋穿上  母乳吸完
We will. Got my dancing shoes, got my breast pump.
狂欢开始
Let's party.
如果你在酒吧里吸奶
You know, if you pump at the bar,
我保证我们一定有免费酒水喝
I promise we'll get free drinks.
有问题就打给我
Call if there's any problems.
不许  她很忙  打给霍华德
No. She's busy. You call Howard.
知道了
Got it.
打给我  别打给霍华德
Call me. Don't call Howard.
我决不会打给霍华德
I would never call Howard.
好了  与其整晚斗嘴
Okay, instead of arguing all night,
不如分分工如何照顾宝宝
let's just split up the baby chores.
好的  上半身的嘴交给我来喂
Yeah, great. Um, I'll put food in her top half,
下半身拉的屎尿交给你来清
you deal with whatever comes out the bottom.
真不敢相信我们得请谢尔顿
I can't believe we have to ask Sheldon
回去帮忙我们
to come back and help us.
你有我惨吗
Oh, boo-hoo.
我花了四千大洋买的礼物
I spent four grand on a gift
结果只能摆脱他一个下午
that only got rid of him for an afternoon.
那是什么声音
What is that?
我不知道  但如果他大喊
I don't know, but if he yells,
"它是活的"  我们就赶紧跑
"It's alive," we run.
你们要是敲门了  我也听不见
If you knocked, I couldn't hear you.
我在焊接火车头呢
I'm welding this locomotive engine.
你们要是没敲门  拜托有点基本礼仪好吗
And if you didn't knock, how about some manners?
你是怎么把这玩意弄上楼的
How'd you even get that up the stairs?
我不断鼓励自己  "你行的  你行的"
I said to myself, "I think I can, I think I can."
结果我不行  于是...
And then I couldn't, so...
我花钱请了两个答应不会来抢我们的人搬的
I paid two men who promised not to come rob us later.
听着  谢尔顿  上校想让我们
Okay, look, Sheldon, the Colonel wants us
把导向系统做得更小一点
to make the guidance system smaller,
没有你我们做不到
and we can't do it without you.
有意思
Interesting.
这么说我是正确的
Well, so I was right.
快开窗  有人马上要释放婊气了
Open a window. It's about to get smug in here.
本来我会很愿意帮助你们
Well, I would love to help you,
但自从我体会到了
but since I discovered the satisfaction
动手调适火车头引擎的的满足感
of working with my hands on a train engine,
我觉得我无法再回去搞理论了
I don't think I can go back to theory.
现在我是一名工程师了
I'm an engineer now.
先把话说清楚
And, hey, just to be clear,
是火车驾驶员[工程师]
a train engineer.
不是你那种蠢蛋工程师
Not that goofy kind you are.
谢尔顿  你几周后再去旅行也不迟啊
Sheldon, you can still go on the trip in a few weeks.
帮帮我们吧
Just help us out.
抱歉  我得继续研究这个火车头
Sorry. I need to work on this engine
这样我到铁路站场时才不会看起来像白痴
so when I get to the train yard I won't look foolish.
他居然担心自己看起来像白痴
He's worried about looking foolish.
这是何等讽刺啊
That's a Heapin' helpin' of irony right there.
拜托  你明知道自己不会放弃物理
Come on, you know you're not leaving physics.
你这一出到底是为哪般啊
Why are you doing this?
莱纳德  在理论物理的世界里
Leonard, in the world of theoretical physics,
永远得不到结论  无法证明的东西太多了
you never finish; so much is unprovable.
但在我学习那本铁路指南的时候
But when I was studying that railway guide,
是那么真实可触  是那么令人满足
it was so tangible and so satisfying
和我"咔"一声一拍即合
that something just clicked.
然后又"嗒"一声
Then it clacked.
然后"咔嗒  咔嗒"
Then it clicked, then it clacked,
"咔嗒  咔嗒"  火车来啦
click-clack clickety-clack, and here we are.
加州理工的幼儿园给你回复了吗
Did you hear anything back from the Caltech preschool?
还没  不过我们会申请很多其他幼儿园
Not yet, but we're gonna apply to a bunch of others
不会在一棵树上吊死
just to keep our options open.
够了  别再聊幼儿园的事了
Okay, stop that! No more preschool talk.
今晚的重点是玩得开心
Tonight is about having fun.
没什么比被你训更开心了
Nothing says fun like being scolded.
是拉杰
It's Raj.
一切都还好吗
Everything okay?
别担心  一切都好
Don't worry. Everything's fine.
把电话挂了  我们不需要帮助
Hang up! We don't need help.
我不需要你帮我决定  我们需不需要帮助
I don't need your help deciding when we need help!
拉杰  怎么了
Raj, what's going on?
是这样的
Yes, so,
我刚刚在帮哈雷热奶
I was just warming up some milk for Halley,
我觉得奶闻起来有点怪味
and I-I thought it smelled a little funky,
所以我看了你写在奶瓶上的日期
so I checked the date that you wrote on the bottle,
结果上面写的是"星期囧"
and it says "Flerbsday."
写的是"星期二"
It says "Tuesday."
这怎么可能是"二"
How is that a "T"?!
我很肯定奶没变质  但如果你担心
I'm sure it's fine, but if you're worried,
冰箱里还有新的
there's extra milk in the freezer.
好的好的
Okay, yes,
为了万无一失
I will err on the side of caution
我就解冻新的吧
and defrost a fresh batch.
你白白浪费了一瓶没变质的奶
You're wasting perfectly good milk.
-好  那你喝了它  -奶而已我怕什么
- Fine, you drink it. - It's just milk.
斯图尔特  不准你喝老娘的奶
Stuart, don't you drink my milk!
给我
Okay, give-
你俩到底能不能搞定
Can you guys handle this or not?
我们当然能搞定
Oh, of course we can.
你们几个姑娘玩得开心点
Uh, you girls have a good time.
她说这里我说了算
She said I was in charge.
所以我们就这么把这瓶奶倒了吗
So we just throw this away?
不然还能怎么办
What else are you gonna do with it?
加在咖啡里吗
Put it in your coffee?
我喝咖啡的确加奶啊
Well, I don't take it black.
好的  他写在板子上的全部内容都在这了
Okay. This is everything he had on the board.
我很肯定我们能补全这个理论
I'm sure we can figure the rest out.
好
All right.
你尽管开口打断我
Feel free to jump in.
我除了哼一声也没啥想法了
"Hmm" is all I got.
我们能做到
Oh, we can get this.
会不会是我把上下弄颠倒了
Is there any chance it's upside-down?
或许我们可以找其他理论物理学家来帮忙
Maybe we can find another theoretical physicist to help us.
这是机密研究项目
It's classified.
如果我们告诉其他人会惹上麻烦的
If we tell anyone, we'd get in trouble.
至少我想出了这个主意  还哼了一声
Hey, I came up with that and "Hmm."
你屁都没贡献
You haven't pitched anything.
接着琢磨吧
Just keep thinking.
我想到了
I got it.
你真的琢磨出来了吗
You really figured it out?
没有
No,
但只要我们让谢尔顿看到这堆鬼扯
but when we show this nonsense to Sheldon,
他会被逼疯  然后会忍不住纠正我们
it will make him crazy, and he'll have to fix it.
你真是天才
Oh, you're a genius.
是啊  我知道
Yeah, I know.
这个根本连数学符号都不是
That's not even a math symbol.
是卡通角色查理·布朗的头发
That's just Charlie Brown's hair.
抱歉  姑娘们
Sorry, guys.
这间夜店本来很火的
This club was so great.
怎么就改建成书店了呢
How could they turn it into a bookstore?
我还以为人类已经彻底摆脱书店了
I thought we got rid of all those.
现在觉得文艺复兴合唱团听起来挺有趣了吧
Renaissance Choir's looking pretty good right now, huh?
怎么了
Hello?
没什么可担心的
Nothing to worry about.
只是她哭了好一阵了
She's just been crying for a little while,
我想知道你有没有什么哄她睡觉的小技巧
and I was wondering if you had any tricks to get her to sleep.
她本来睡得好好的  你非要和她一起自拍
She was sleeping just fine till you took a selfie with her!
她吹了个口水泡泡
She was blowing a spit bubble.
那么可爱你让我怎么忍
It was adorable!
你们能搞定吗  要不要我回家去
You guys got this? Do you need me to come home?
等一下
Wait.
她哭得没那么厉害了
She's settling down.
没事了  只是误报
Oh, okay, false alarm.
分享一点育儿经验
Little parenting tip:
睡着的宝宝讨厌被人开闪光灯拍照
sleeping babies hate flash photography.
没什么事吧
Is everything okay?
没事
Yeah.
我可能把我襁褓中的女儿
I may have just left my infant daughter
留给了海绵宝宝和派大星这对活宝
with Patrick and SpongeBob.
附近还有另一间夜店
Hey, there's another dance club nearby.
不知道你们是否喜欢拉丁音乐
I mean, I don't know how you feel about Latin music,
但根据他们的营业时间  现在还没关门
but according to their horas of operacion, they're open.
要不今晚到此为止吧
Maybe we should just call it a night.
确定吗  他们两点才关门哦
You sure? They're open till dos.
是啊  我们都精心打扮了
Yeah, we're all dressed up.
回家可惜了
Why go home?
我只是没心情了
I'm just not really in the mood anymore.
你怎么了
What's going on with you?
不知道  只是觉得
I don't know. This is all starting to feel
想抓住青春的尾巴挺伤感的
like a sad attempt to recapture our youth.
我不伤感
I'm not sad.
我只想喝醉  不用穿宽松的运动裤
I just wanted to get drunk and not wear sweatpants.
我也不伤感
I'm not sad.
瞧瞧
I mean, hello.
也许是我伤感
Okay, maybe I'm the one who's sad.
你伤感什么呢
What are you sad about?
也许是因为你生了孩子
Maybe the fact that you went and had a baby.
我生了孩子你不高兴吗
You're upset I had a baby?
当然不是  我只是...
No, of course not. I just...
我没想到会让我有这么多的感触
I didn't think it would make me have all these feelings.
什么感触
What feelings?
压力
Pressure!
她在找幼儿园
I mean, she's looking at preschools,
她有厢式车  她有401K[退休账户]
she has a minivan, she has a 401k.
她没解释前  我以为这是一个种族
Before she talked about it, I just thought that was a race.
你觉得这些东西很有趣吗
You think that stuff is fun?
为人父母令人害怕
Being a parent is terrifying.
我时时担心  刻刻疲倦
I'm constantly worried, I'm always tired,
过一会儿  我得在书店的停车场
and in a few minutes, I'm gonna milk myself
把奶泵出来
in a bookstore parking lot.
我明白
I get that, okay?
只是我和莱纳德结婚两年了
It's just, Leonard and I have been married for two years,
我们和约会时相比  没有任何进展
and we're no further along than when we were dating.
别这样
Come on.
你有很多值得开心的事
You've got so much to feel good about.
你现在有份好工作
You've got a great job now.
我想我的薪水是还不错
Yeah, I guess I am making decent money.
你赚的钱比我多
You make more than I do.
虽说你们还没买房子  但你们的公寓非常棒
You may not have a house yet, but your apartment's great.
比我的公寓大
It's bigger than mine.
莱纳德深爱着你  娶了你两次
And Leonard loves you so much, he married you twice.
我连一次订婚经历都没有
I'm not even engaged once.
我甚至不知道谢尔顿是否考虑过婚姻
I don't even know if Sheldon thinks about marriage.
我年纪越来越大了
I'm not getting any younger.
说实话  我现在在想
Honestly, I kind of thought by now,
也许我们...
we might have had some sort of...
小心  哭泣声会让我分泌乳汁
Careful. The sound of crying can make me lactate.
对不起  我忍不住
I'm sorry. I can't help it.
这下我也想哭了
Oh, that's gonna make me cry.
果然出来了
And there they go.
谢尔顿  原来我们根本不需要你
Well, Sheldon, turns out we didn't need you after all.
没错  我们自己解决了
That's right. We figured it out all by ourselves.
也没那么难
Wasn't even that hard.
两位真厉害
Well, good for you guys.
看  我手上有油污  但我都不在乎
Look, I have a grease smudge on my hand, and I'm okay with it.
你不看看白板吗  看我们多正确
Aren't you gonna look at the board to see how right we are?
不用  多谢  我忙着修这个燃油泵
No, thanks. I'm busy trying to fix this fuel pump.
那是歧管
It's a manifold.
那看来修好了
Well, I guess it's fixed.
快看下白板
Just look at the board.
错了
That's wrong.
不是吧
Oh, no!
那要怎么改正呢
What should we have done differently?
首先  在同一方程中
Well, first of all, you can't use relativistic
不能使用相对和非相对向量
and non-relativistic vectors in the same equation.
跟你说过了
Told ya.
你能纠正我们吗
Can you fix it for us?
好  但是下不为例
Okay, but this is the last time.
小瞧哥了  蠢货
Nice try, blockheads.
拜托  谢尔顿  你不能就这样放弃物理
Come on, Sheldon. You can't turn your back on physics.
而且你根本不知道你在捣鼓些什么
Besides, you have no idea what you're doing with this stuff.
如果你真想学机械方面的知识
But if you really want to learn the mechanical side,
你想知道的  我都能教你
I can teach you anything you want to know.
与其站着傻看
And instead of standing around watching,
你不如帮我们创建更小的导向系统
you can help us build your smaller guidance system.
有了新的技能
And with all these new skills,
你可以修好任何火车模型
you'd be able to fix any model train.
你将成为火车模型店之王
You'd be the king of the train store!
不好意思  哥有女朋友
Excuse me. I have a girlfriend.
哥已经是火车模型店之王了
I'm already king of the train store.
怎么样
So, what do you say?
我能有什么选择  你们需要我
Oh, what choice do I have? You need me.
我就像这个团队的曲轴
I'm like the crankshaft of this team.
那是涡轮增压机
That's a turbo.
无论是什么  看起来很沉
Well, whatever it is, it looks heavy.
你们两个在艾米回家前把它抬楼下去
I'm gonna need you two to get it downstairs before Amy comes home.
抱歉这里这么热
I apologize that it's so warm in here.
的确很热
It is warm in here.
我都流汗了
I've worked up a bit of a sweat.
我也是
Me, too.
水能给我吗
May I borrow your water?
* 大爷在此 *
* Here I am *
* 像飓风般震撼你 *
* Rock you like a hurricane *
* 大爷在此 *
* Here I am *
* 像飓风般震撼你 *
* Rock you like a hurricane *
绿灯了
The light's green.
对不起
Sorry.
导航说还有三小时就到铁路了
GPS says we'll be at the railway in three hours.
我能在两小时内开到
I can get us there in two.